NARESH BELLO

Washington, DC · Phone 954-591-0747

nareshbello@gmail.com · LinkedIn https://bit.ly/3cH0TwN; Art Portfolio https://bit.ly/3B8Y54X

Self-motivated, detail oriented UX/UI designer with excellent communications, presentation and problem-solving skills seeking a position with a team of motivated professionals to best utilize me skills and strengths to achieve organizational goals and objectives. Background in Graphic design with a Bachelor of Art Degree from Florida Atlantic University and holds a Certificate in UX/UI Design through George Washington University.

PROJECTS

Lead UX/UI DESIGNER, THE KINDNESS PROJECT

Redesign of the Kindness Project mobile registration page allowing new users to smoothly register with The Kindness Project an organization that supports their foster families with essential items. The Lead UX/UI Designer responsibilities included organizing and managing four team members to maintain a steady workflow and timely delivery of the project. Communicated with stake holders to understand requirements and provide creative thoughtful solutions. This project included research, prototype, communication, and presentation to the client. The client approved the redesign and will update the mobile website.

TKP Prototype https://bit.ly/3cCAOz7

UX/UI Designer, Unofficial Instagram Guide redesign

Redesign of Instagram's Guide feature to create a user-friendly interface allowing users to navigate places, explore and read about experiences uploaded by local users. As a UX/UI Designer on this project the responsibilities included conducting user research, creating personas, affinity diagram, user flows, journey mapping, guerilla testing, wireframes, layout design, prototyping, and presentation.

Instagram Guide redesign https://bit.ly/3KXKMrx

EXPERIENCE

JUL 2021 - NOV 2021

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, ELEGANT BUT RAW

Collaborating with six team members in various cities and different time zones to successfully create weekly Social Media Content based on current top three grossing songs and upcoming releases.

Creating 20 plus social media graphic designs, preparing rough sketches, and illustrations for design content.

Working directly with the client to develop layout, style and design concept for the Album cover entitled "New Beginnings".

Album cover https://spoti.fi/3RzCl7Y

Dec 2020 - April 2021

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, Be Involved in Government Club

Designing logo for Club to be used on social media pages, T shirts and merchandize.

Be Involved in Government Club Instagram posts https://bit.ly/3q7EJXF

Jan 2021 - April 2021

Member of the committee, BAFAU Committee

Collaborating with the committee and faculty to design the BAFAU 2021 Art Show. In this position the task was to review and critique student's websites and provide feedback to the community.

April 2016 - Oct 2019

Part Time, South Florida Chevy Dealers

Working with local Chevy dealer as a crew member to set up shoots to develop TV commercials, and promos. Creating promotional digital advertising for local dealer. Assisting in the distribution of marketing materials at local Chevy sponsored events.

EDUCATION

AUG 2022

UX/UI CERTIFICATE, GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY

APRIL 2021

BACHELOR OF ART, IN STUDIO ART, FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Visual design, Typography, Color Theory, Research, ZOOM, Figma, GitHub, MS TEAMS, Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign
- Frontend: GitHub HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and MS VSC IDE